DANIEL TORRES CALVO

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Costa Rica

PHONE

8587-2400

EMAIL

daniel.torres96@hotmail.com

DATE OF BIRTH

27/04/1996

DRIVING LICENSE

B1

LINKS

LinkedIn

<u>Portfolio</u>

<u>GitHub</u>

SKILLS

Teamwork

Communication

Proactive

Self-motivation

Troubleshooting

Mentoring

LANGUAGES

Spanish

• • • •

English B2

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

HOBBIES

Movies

Beach

Read

Music

Travel

PROFILE

Experience building web applications. With knowledge about user interfaces, testing, and debugging processes. Proficient in an assortment of technologies including Java, JavaScript and excellent experience of relational databases. Able to work productively in a team in agile environments.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Software Developer, Accenture

Heredia

Aug 2021 — Present

Back-end development with Java Spring and technologies such as Spring Boot, Maven, AEM, JCR, JPA, GraphQL, JUnit, Mockito, etc. Creation of new endpoints, services and resolution of problems that affect the existing integration. Develop OSGi service components to integrate with backend systems usign RESTful APIs. Work on several projects providing solutions that follows best practices with coding standards, unit testing and continuous integration.

Software Developer, SysCo Consultores de Sistemas

San José

Nov 2019 — Aug 2021

Full-stack development with Java Spring and other technologies like Spring Boot, Maven, Spring Data, JSP, JavaScript, SASS and Oracle database. Gained experience building customer facing web based applications, web services RESTful and code collaboration in teams using GIT and SVN. Able to implement solutions to new and existing projects according to the product owner's needs.

EDUCATION

Licentiate's degree, Computer Engineering, Universidad Nacional de Costa Rica

Feb 2021 — Present

In progress

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering, Universidad Nacional de Costa Rica

Feb 2019 — Nov 2019

Diploma's degree, Computer Programming, Universidad Nacional de Costa Rica

Feb 2014 — Nov 2018